<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Parasito</string>
    <string name="for_new_players">For New Players</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_human">How to play Human</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_alien">How to play Alien</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_psion">How to play Psion</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_android">How to play Android</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_syndicate">How to play Syndicate</string>
    <string name="locations">Locations</string>
    <string name="game_events">Game Events</string>
    <string name="title_activity_locations">LocationsActivity</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="modes">Modes</string>
    <string name="places">Places</string>
    <string name="sub_roles">Sub\-Roles</string>
    <string name="classic">Classic</string>
    <string name="zeta">Zeta</string>
    <string name="chaos">Chaos</string>
    <string name="station">The Station</string>
    <string name="level1">Level 1: Cargo Bay</string>
    <string name="level2">Level 2: Living Quarters</string>
    <string name="level3">Level 3: Biosphere</string>
    <string name="level4">Level 4: Med bay</string>
    <string name="level5">Level 5: Weapons Center</string>
    <string name="level6">Level 6: Networking and Mechs</string>
    <string name="level7">Level 7: The Bridge</string>
    <string name="reactorLevel">Reactor Level</string>
    <string name="coreLevel">The Core</string>
    <string name="spaceWalk">Spacewalk</string>
    <string name="vents">Ventilation Shaft</string>
    <string name="thor">Military Station Thor</string>
    <string name="planet">Desert Planet</string>
    <string name="DSM">Deep Space Miner</string>
    <string name="SG">Security Guard</string>
    <string name="Doc">Chief Medical Officer</string>
    <string name="CWO">Chief Weapons Officer</string>
    <string name="CMO">Chief Mechs Officer</string>
    <string name="CIO">Chief Intelligence Officer</string>
    <string name="Captain">Captain</string>
    <string name="CEO">Chief Engineer Officer</string>
    <string name="early_game">Early Game</string>
    <string name="mid_game">Mid Game</string>
    <string name="late_game">Late Game</string>
    <string name="dangers">Dangers</string>
    <string name="general_tactics">General Tactics</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="evolution">Evolution</string>
    <string name="alignment">Alignment</string>
    <string name="abilities">Abilities</string>
    <string name="upgrades">Upgrades</string>
    <string name="directive">Directive</string>
    <string name="sabotage">Sabotage</string>
    <string name="for_new_players_about">
        It\'s a game about murder and deception. You and your fellow crew members on the station are stranded on an unknown space sector.
        But you\'re not alone. With you is an alien organism seeking to destroy you. It could be any one of you.
        Will this enemy prevail or will you eliminate it?
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_modes_classic">
        In this gamemode, there are only 2 major roles: Humans and Alien.\n
        Alien can infect humans to create spawns and by doing so win by spawning everyone.
        Other way for alien to win this scenario is to kill all humans.\n Humans\' only way to victory is to kill the alien, and it\'s spawns.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_modes_zeta">
        This gamemode gives you more major roles to play with; Psion, Android and Syndicates.\n\n
        Psion: This role is a human with psychic powers. It has a choice to go good,neutral or evil alignment.\n
        Evil alignment\'s goal is to destroy everyone else. Good\'s alignment is to help humans.
        And neutral is&#8230; well neutral. Just survive and you\'re good.\n\n
        Android\'s role is determined by RNG, It gets it\'s goal, or how it is referred to in the game, Directive.\n
        This directive can be: Preserve Alien, Eliminate Humanity or Preserve Humanity.\n\n
        The third and final role is Syndicate.\n In this role you\'re playing as a human, but with a mafia\-esque kind of background and goal.
        Their goal is to sabotage the station and to murder all non\-syndicate crew members.
        To differentiate from humans, they have a stash they can place at the start of the game.
        Stash by itself is invisible and is usually placed in a well\-hidden place.\n\n
        In this gamemode, there can\'t be both alien and syndicates in the game. Only one of the 2.
        Android and Psion role have a chance to appear. There might be a Zeta game without any of those.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_modes_chaos">
        Just like zeta gamemode, you have access to all roles. However, syndicate and alien roles both exist, as well as psion and android.
        Leaving you with 6 humans, and, well&#8230; 6 other\-roled players.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_places_station">
        The station is one of the two main locations of this map. It is sectioned into 9 different levels:
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_places_level1">
        On this level you\'ll fine all 8 spaceships, a recycler, a solarite processor, an Auto-doc and a bunch of crates.
        It has spacewalk access, as well as elevators leading to Level 2, and Reactor Level
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_places_level2">
        This level is where all players start the game. It holds a Marshall\'s office,
        where Security Guards can look at cameras and upgrade station security. Also houses a Teleporter which can teleport a player to Thor and Planet.\n
        This level has elevators leading to Level 3 and Level 1. Express elevators lead to Reactor level and Core level.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_places_level3">
        Here is what players refer to as \"The Zoo\". Animal life here can be infested by the alien that gives him powerful mindless minions.
        If such situation is ignored, the station can get infested rather quickly.\n
        There is also the alien holding pen, from which you can do an experiment on live alien specimen,
        a Psionic research room, for psi\-research and an Auto-doc.\n
        Elevators lead to Level 2 and Level 4, also has Spacewalk access.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_places_level4">
        This level holds a gene modifier vendor, Medical research station which has an Auto-doc next to it,
        and a Blood tester used to identify Alien lifeform.\n
        Elevators lead to Level 3 and Level 5.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_places_level5">
        Here is where you can upgrade your weapons at the Weapon Upgrade Station, or upgrade the Station Weapons.
        Elevators lead to Level 4 and Level 6, has Spacewalk access.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_places_level6">
        This is where you can find an Armory, where you can upgrade your persona. You can also research Mechs and Station Firmware.\n
        Elevators lead to Level 5 and Level 7, also has express elevators leading to Reactor Level and Core Level.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_places_level7">
        This is where the station captain resides in. Nobody usually goes here without reason. Unless the reason is to kill the captain.
        Has elevator that leads to Level 6 and an express elevator leading to Reactor Level.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_places_reactorLevel">
        Reactor Level is home 2 power links and a transformer which can be interacted with. To cut the power or restore it.
        On this level you can also find the Oxygen generator, which can be turned on/off
        There\'s an elevator leading to Level 1, and 3 express elevators leading to Level 2, Level 6 and Level 7.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_places_theCore">
        This is where the station\'s AI resides in. From here you can produce autonomous robots that act like station security.
        This is also where the Android can upgrade. Express elevators lead to Level 6 and Level 2.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_places_spaceWalk">
        Spacewalk is where you can find the Station\'s Radar dish, which, if destroyed, disables the ability to do Crew or Alien scans.
        It also connects Level 1, Level 3 and Level 5.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_places_ventilationShafts">
        It\'s a maze which connects all levels. All crew members can use them for a faster travel, but more dangerous
        as there is no surveillance or protection from station security.\nThe Vents are divided into 2 sections: Odd vents and Even vents.\n
        Named as such because they connect odd/even levels.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_places_planet">
        Second main location of the map. Has a bunker which contains all the vendors you might need. There are also caves with infested cocoons and solarite veins.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_places_thor">
        Second station that can enter the sector at any time. It\'s a small station with maintenance shaft and a teleporter.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_roles_DSM">
        As a miner, your job is to recycle unused items found from crates in the station.
        Recycler is found on Level 1. After 5 minutes, you can launch into space using one of those spaceships.
        Use those to mine mineral clusters found floating in space.
        Doing so increases your entire crew\'s income while getting you money.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_roles_SG">
        As a security guard, your job is to upgrade station\'s security in Marshall\'s office.
        Besides that, you\'re to patrol the station and suppress any infestation happening (most likely on Level 3).\n
        Killing alien minions gives you money.Also, you get extra health.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_roles_Doc">
        As a doctor, your job is to:\n
        a)Lock the zoo,psi-research room and the alien containment room on Level 3.\n
        b)Perform experiment on contained Alien specimen on Level 3.\n
        c)Unlock the Blood Tester on Level 4.\n
        d)Do research on Level 4.\n
        e)Do psi-research on Level 3.\n
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_roles_CWO">
        As a Sargent, your job is to unlock the Weapon Upgrade Station and do research on Level 5.
        Given that this role has lowest income out of them all, it\'s customary to let other people
        come in and do some research for you.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_roles_CMO">
        As a Major, you\'re to upgrade mechs on level 6, as well as unlocking the Armory on the same level.\n
        Once you get a mech, take the flamethrower one and patrol the vents with it. It is much safer that way.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_roles_CIO">
        As a Lieutenant, you\'re to lock the Blood Tester room on level 4.\n
        Usually you do research on Level 6, but you can replace someone if they went missing.\n
        Given that this role has highest income, and gains more income with each research made.
        A better tactic might be to grab all of the low-cost researches as soon as possible.
        (Eg. Recycler unlock at Level 1.)
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_roles_Captain">
        As the captain of the station and the crew, your job is to oversee everything going on the station
        by looking through the cameras on Level 7. Occasionally drop down to 6 to do research for Station Firmware.\n
        Beware that you don\'t get murdered for that Captain Keycard you have in your inventory.
    </string>
    <string name="for_new_players_roles_CEO">
        As an Engineer, you\'re in charge of upgrading the Station Reactor on the Reactor Level, and start production of
        droids on Core Level.\n
        You\'re also assigned to do repairs on the station whenever needed.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_human_early_game">
        In early game, you want to get to your job site as soon as possible.
        Sooner you get there, the sooner you get to do work, which in turn means you get more money quicker.
        At this point it would somewhat be safe in the vents. If you do meet the Alien Host.\n
        Don\'t engage unless you\'re in a pair. If you get crabbed, don\'t panic. Just go to the nearest auto-doc station
        and you\'ll be fine.\n
        Don\'t get trapped in a room with someone with no way out. There\'s no telling what might happen.\n\n
        At around 5 minutes, miners should be out of the station and mining.
        If they\'re not, force them to go mine. Their mining operation is crucial to the entire
        crew for income.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_human_mid_game">
        Mid game, which would be something like 20 minutes.
        At this point you\'d have earned a lot of money, upgraded your station quite a bit, if not the whole way.\n
        At this point, if not sooner, you might consider upgrading yourself at the Armory, or Weapon Upgrade Station or Gene Modifier.\b
        Traversing the vents is a risk.\n\n
        In case you are tagged, consider investing some money in either a cloaking device
        found in Equipment vendors, or Night Dweller gene from Gene Modifier.\n
        Invisibility might be a very good tool against aliens who can\'t transform to human form.
        This is because most of such forms do not have detection.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_human_late_game">
        Late game, or end game in some cases. You\'re to look for a
        way to battle the evil in the way that it will give you advantage,
        even if it means destroying the station. Just before doing so,
        do the upgrades and whatever you need beforehand. Because when the
        station is gone, there is no way to research anything new.
        Knowing what form the alien is can win you the fight. Find out
        and use this knowledge to your advantage
        (weakness and strengths of certain alien forms.)\n
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_human_dangers">
        Destroying alien eggs will get you crabbed, unless you\'re in a mech.\n
        Entering vents while vent decontamination is happening is a bad idea.\n
        Beware of who may be hiding in steam vents.\n
        Have a way of detection as soon as possible, cloaking is serious business.\n
        Try not to get cornered.\n
        The station getting destroyed early on is very fatal for human\'s victory.\n
        If oxygen generator gets turned off, your top priority should be getting it back on.\n
        If your energy starts draining without any obvious reason, go to auto-doc ASAP.\n
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_alien_general_tactic">
        In early game, the alien host form is very weak, therefore you shouldn\'t engage in combat
        you can\'t win. Around 3 minute mark, you can release the alien specimens from Level 3, try getting into there unseen.
        Break through to the zoo (if locked) and infest the animals, watch the whole thing spread and maybe play the chaos
        into your advantage. Gain a spawn or 2. See how it goes.\n
        Doing research as your role while alien will cause said research to be infested, you can check the bonuses you gain at the research console.\n\n
        Do not play passive. That tactic almost never works!\n
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_alien_evolution">
        Pick your evolutions depending on the situations, not what you want to try.
        If android is still around and is deemed as a big threat, you might consider going into Voltaic route.\n\n

        Alien has 2 main evolution routes:\n
        1) Body - allows the Alien to infest life support structures on each level.
        Infesting one will cause it to spawn alien minions (like infesting zoo did, but less powerful) and continue
        to spread creep. Will also allow you burrow.\n

        2) Mind - allows the Alien to go invisible for undetermined time. But be wary, that invisibility is still noticeable
        on players\'s screens, because Starcraft 2. You can also build shrines which will mind\-fest nearby humans. This type
        of infestation is not visually visible, but it is visible by the energy draining of the target. Once it\'s energy goes to 0
        said target becomes your subordinate spawn.\n\n

        From that point on, you choose the sub-routes how you see fit.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_alien_dangers">
        By no means fight someone with a flamethrower weapon as initial Alien Host form. That is a suicide.
        Avoid security guards as initial host, they have extra health, making them even more dangerous than an average crew member.\n
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_alien_tips">
        Leaving your eggs out in the open may damage your evolution progress, but destroying the eggs causes the targets to be crabbed.
        This could play into your hands if you play it smart.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_psion_alignment">
        Alignment plays a huge part for psion. It basically tells him what his goal is. Once you get past 10 alignment positive or negative, you can\'t go back.\n
        Alignment is obtained by killing humans(negative) or alien(positive), and by choosing your abilities.\n
        Once psion reaches past 10 alignment, either good abilities or evil abilities get locked. Making you not able to pick those abilities anymore.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_psion_abilities">
        Abilities are grouped up in 3 categories:\n
        Good Alignment abilities are centered around group support. Making psion something like a healer, but also a nuker.\n
        Evil Alignment abilities are centered around damage output. Making psion damage dealer of epic proportions.\n
        Neutral Alignment abilities are something in between mobility and self-preservation.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_psion_general_tactic">
        Depending if good aligned or evil. You might want to reveal yourself to the rest of the crew.
        Most players deem that if psion identifies himself earlier that he is good, but to take safety measures they still test you.

        As an evil psion, don\'t be afraid to be the first one to pull the trigger in 1v1 scenario.
        With telekinetic grasp and lightning ability, you can pretty easily deal a lot of damage.
        Combine that with a right weapon, you can kill a person pretty quickly, whitout him outting your identity.\n
        As a psionic being, your weakness is Pulse Rifle, which deals extra damage to shields and psionic targets.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_psion_tips">
        You can get extra ability points by sabotaging psi-research on Level 3.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_android_directive">
        Directive is what dictates what goal you have in the game.
        There are 3 different directives:\n
        1) Destroy humanity.\n
        2) Protect Humanity.\n
        3) Preserve Alien Lifeform.\n
        The last directive gives you access to alien communication channels.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_android_upgrades">
        Upgrades is how android gets stronger. There are 2 types of upgrades.
        First which are dubbed as  \"Sleeper Upgrades\". Such upgrades are done on your human-like form but can carry on to the other upgrades.
        Second which are Chassis Upgrades. Changing your form completely, which grants you different stats and abilities.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_android_tips">
        Dying is a bit different for Android. Upon death you drop a Memory chip which can hop around for a bit.
        It has to reach The Core to repair itself, or be brought there.
        Upon when the person who brought it gets a remote controller to turn the android on or off.
        However, your directive still takes top priority.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_android_general_tactic">
        Depending on your directive you might want to reveal yourself to the rest of the crew.
        Good droids are still periodically tested by the captain by getting targeted.
        Although turrets cannot attack you thanks to the Core.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_syndicate_early_game">
        In early game, you should place down your stash in some remote location where it\'s not so easy to find. Given, the stash does have cloaking.
        However, cloaked units are easily spotted, it\'s only a matter of having detection. You should also grab the Syndicate Communication Relay in
        order to talk to your teammates. It makes planning easier.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_syndicate_general_tactic">
        Grouping up and just collectively murdering people seems like a good tactic, too bad not many use it.
        Murder as many people as possible and just try to keep it down low.\n
        Calling for a Syndicate Assault Pod is good for a more direct assault approach. Think of it as reinforcements.\n
        Setting up a powersink is also valid option to murder the station as people cannot perform the \"Saber\-test\" which requires Weapons 5.
        Therefore you\'re forcing the game into a deathmatch.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_syndicate_sabotage">
        Sabotaging by researching may be good, may not be, depending on what Human sub\-role you got.
        Sabotaging in terms of destroying Security Boxes in vents is always a good idea for evil.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_play_syndicate_tips">
        Always attack in a pair or more.\n
        You can mindwipe a crew member and make him become a syndicate member.
        Always use whatever syndicate sub-role bonus you\'ve got. These are very useful.
    </string>
</resources>
